A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
The camellia blossom, also known as Tsubaki, is a flower without fragrance.
It proclaims nothing, blooming in silence.
When the blossom's petals scatter, it is quietly tragic.
Hey, Tsubaki, what do you feel like playing?
I want to play ball.
I am Tsubaki, a silent flower without fragrance.
It proclaims a Sam
Would you like to love this song?
Next we are picking up.
Oops.
Hoping to return at 5.
深追いしすぎた眩しさが悪い夢に続いても
繋いだ魂の火が胸を刺すなら 言葉よりもっと強い響きが今聞こえるか
出会った訳は途絶びに引き付けられて 触れた瞬間の傷の分だけ確かになれる
The Enchanted Sword Masamune.
If he continues like this for much longer, he will become a Kishin.
Are you sure you're ready for this, Tsubaki?
You know how difficult a battle it's going to be.
I'll stop Masamune.
Difficult or not, I can do it.
What does Black Star have to say about it?
I haven't told him everything, if that's what you mean.
He doesn't need to know the whole story yet.
But he said he's willing to put his soul in my hands for this battle.
Did he?
You've got yourself a good partner there, don't you?
Yes.
The Enchanted Sword Masamune.
Break the soul possession.
A heart sings in the rain?
Huh.
I wonder what Professor Stein is up to canceling class like this.
Think he's skipping so he can dissect something?
There's no telling with that guy.
But don't worry about it.
Today will be cool.
Especially without Captain Spass.
I'm guessing you mean Black Star.
Hey, Tsubaki isn't here either.
Oh, Maka, haven't you heard?
Huh?
Heard what?
It's all over school.
Someone overheard the teachers talking in the faculty room earlier.
Apparently Black Star and Tsubaki went off to collect the soul of the Enchanted Sword Masamune.
Enchanted Sword?
I hope they're okay.
It's gonna be tough.
They say the sword is on the verge of becoming a Kishin.
So, uh, where are we?
This is Shen, also known as the Village of Needles.
Why do you think a little out of the way village like this would become a target for the Enchanted Sword?
I'm not sure.
Frightened Souls seem to be more likely to become the Enchanted Sword's targets.
Maybe the villagers are afraid of something.
Huh.
Black Star, there's something I need to tell you.
It's about the Enchanted Sword.
I haven't exactly explained everything yet.
Whoa!
What?
What's that?
Uh, Black Star?
Yahoo!
Black Star on stage!
Front and Center!
Yeah!
Please try not to break that.
A big star is here to perform in your tiny village!
Come on out everybody!
Why are you diolling Black Star?
Hey kid.
Huh?
Just what do you think you're doing up there?
you think you're doing up there do you realize you're standing on top of the
village's guardian did it so you're targeting the old folks first
what was that young lady elderly I'm still as active as ever all day and all
life there you see that he's definitely the enchanted sword he's definitely not
the enchanted sword what's going on you come to visit the old-timer my what if we
here friends of Ryoku's come to visit
what do you want with our village you've come here to kill more people haven't
you I know that tattoo on your shoulder you're a member of the star clan don't
lie to us boy what did you say the star clan he really say that what the hell are
you doing here you murderer from what I've heard all you star clan members will
do anything for money so why don't you take that get out of our village
okay this village too
damn on top of everything else it's raining finding this stupid enchanted sword would be a lot easier if I could see souls like Maka
but I can't so I'm just gonna have to rely on my other five senses to track the
thing down unfortunately those other senses aren't quite as sharp in a downpour
what happened back there you want to know don't you
no that's not what I was thinking
it's a real long story I'm not a big fan of long stories
right I get it if you'd rather not tell me that's okay
it's happened before remember it was another old man a lot like the one this time
he saw my tattoo and started freaking out I know the tattoo is a symbol of my family the star clan
they were a clan of assassins everybody knew that they would do anything for money
after a while killing people wasn't enough they were hungry for even more power
so they began hunting human souls
but now it's just me I'm the last member of the star clan
I didn't know what happened to the rest of your clan
13 years ago their souls were taken by Lord Death and the Meisters from the academy
at the time I was still just a baby so they didn't take my soul
that's when the school took me in that's it the end
but is it though you don't resent the academy for what they did
nah this was all way back when so long ago that I wasn't even close to being the big star I am now
it was a simple case of cause and effect my old man and old lady crossed a line they shouldn't have
and they paid for it by having their souls taken away
that's all there is to it
yeah I guess
but I still don't like to see people treating you so badly for it
it wasn't your fault
come on are you kidding me
all because of my name I was the center of attention earlier
yahoo
remember a little while ago
when I said I had something I needed to tell you
you don't have to tell me until you're ready
I don't know how you're connected to the enchanted sword
but he's an enemy we have to defeat isn't he
that's all I need to know to fight him
take some time to get whatever's inside you settled
and then you can tell me everything you need to tell
the rain's starting to come down harder
I could stand here thinking
or go sleep
or play
or
eat
Lord Death
I want to know why you sent them after Masamune
wow easy there Meister
who invited you to the death room in the first place
the 118th rule in the death weapon Meister academy handbook states
in the event of an emergency
students are allowed to enter the death room without first obtaining permission
what type of enemy is this enchanted sword father
kid you've come to join the party
the enchanted sword guy is not like the demon sword guy is he
I hope not
the enchanted sword doesn't have a witch with him
he might actually be less dangerous if he was under a witch's supervision
the enchanted sword takes advantage of the fear in people's hearts
he uses that fear in order to take possession of his targets and gain control of their bodies
he then consumes his victim's souls
unless someone stops him
he will become a Keeshan
how could that star clan murderer dare to show up here
will this sickle do any good against someone like him
I'm old enough now to get revenge for what they did
it was those assassins who killed my mother and father
you see I think
and therefore I am
and therefore I eat
hey who are you
I think therefore I eat
you have fear hiding in your soul don't you
fear what would make you think that
yeah
no I don't have any fear
we'll see now won't we
with my power your fear could disappear for good
gone just like that
what do you say
ah Ryoku
so this is where you've been hiding
I brought some stuff we can use as weapons if that assassin comes back
13 years ago we put up those needles
in all that time we haven't had a single thief come along
not that you have anything to worry about
I'll protect the village like I did in the old days
I'm still just as spry as I used to be
no one can take me
who
that's an interesting sword you got
what's a fancy old weapon like that doing in here
Ryoku
are you okay
it's him
let's go
right
no wait Ryoku
what's gotten into you
Ryoku
who is this Ryoku
I am the enchanted sword
Masamune
I think therefore I am hungry
for souls
you're the enchanted sword huh
wait a sec
you're the bratty kid from earlier
the one with the money
what the hell's happening here
it's the soul possession technique
just one thing that sword can do
I've never heard of that before
how's it supposed to work
you know how normal meisters and weapons
match each other's soul wavelengths to unify themselves
the enchanted sword doesn't do that
instead of matching
he simply takes over a person's soul
and controls their body
and when he's finished
the whole soul is devoured
that's the enchanted sword
its blade was so beautiful once
but now that beauty is clouded by darkness
no it's you is it
Subaki
what now
he may be powerful
but he can't control
two soul wavelengths at one time
listen Blackstar
if you shoot your soul wavelength
directly into that void
the enchanted sword will be forced to separate from us
after that leave the rest up to me
just shoot my soul wavelength at him
that's all you want me to do
yes
I joined the academy
in order to hunt down the enchanted sword
this is my fight
and I'm sorry
to put you in the middle Blackstar
Subaki
come on
please tell me that isn't what you're actually thinking
you know better
than that
don't you
weapons and meisters
depend on each other
don't we
you can lean on me
Subaki
and you can do it
a heck of a lot more
than you do now
got it
yes
Puppet Shadow
Blackstar
what the hell was that
you gotta be kidding me
the enchanted sword
can even control
a possessed person's shadow
get him
Puppet
so it's two against one
let's shake this thing
Subaki
ninja sword mode
right
speed star
do this
I'm too fast
you can't catch me
yahoo
can't see me can't you
nope
I bet you can't
and do you know why
because I'm one dude who's way ahead of this time
don't be lucky to even see one hero in my head
wait for just one second
and you'll miss me
that's how fast I am
I think you may want to save speed star for days
when it isn't raining
I'm just a dude who's way ahead of his time
you know
does that mean I was born too early
because time can't keep up with me
man speed star
is way deep
it's all I can do to avoid his attack
I don't have any time to hit him in front of my own
I have to do something
playtime's over
now we fight for real
that's stance
careful black star
he's going to shoot a beam from the sword
now die
puppet thrott
branch out shadow
I'm not done with you
not yet
damn
I'm still ahead
it's not my time yet
come on
is it my time now
subaki
kasaragama
right
now
here we go subaki
okay
let's go full resonance
champ star
I'll do anything to defeat you
you dive relentlessly into destruction
without considering what lies ahead
and now black star has
please
now
mid-air combat is something i'm good at
which makes this
may
Now, Tsubaki! Great!
Blackstar, thank you.
I'll be back.
Oh, interesting.
I see you're planning to come inside, aren't you?
From this point forward, it really is my fight.
I will bring down the enchanted sword.
What just happened?
Tsubaki's gone inside the enchanted sword.
Why would you do that, Tsubaki?
We have to stop this somehow.
What is she thinking?
How is a weapon supposed to fight without her meister?
You don't get it.
The fight is taking place inside their souls.
Anything could happen now.
It had to come to this.
You see, Tsubaki is the only one who can stand against the enchanted sword.
Tsubaki.
You're in.
Make sure you come back.
This is the inside of the sword.
Where are you?
I know what you're going to do.
You'll come after my soul.
You'll try to possess it.
Soul possession?
No, not that.
I think I'll devour your soul just the way it is.
It's so nice to see you.
Tsubaki.
Hi, brother.
Hey, brother.
You've got to die.
You're going after my soul.
You're about to die.
Ready?
So
I